Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Peck School of the Arts, 1936-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- UW-Milwaukee Peck School of the Arts, Office of the Dean Records, 1936-2013, UWM Archival Collection 81; 22.2 cubic ft. (27 boxes including 5 audio reels) 1 oversize folder 2 digital text files (3 MB)
  - New American Cinema Proposal, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Nominating Committee
    - 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1976-1978, 1983-1985, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Opera Theatre, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pellman Theatre Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Peoples' Theatre Company, Personnel Matters, 1976-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Planning and Budget Document, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Planning Document
    - 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 10-19)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1995-1996, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Posters, 1959-1974, 1980-1990, undated (Oversize 1)
  - Posters and Related Materials
    - 1962-1971 (Box 5, Folder 20-29)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Professional Theatre Training Program Brochure, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Program Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Programming
    - General Correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Great Artist Series Brochures, 1988-1996 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Programming Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Materials, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Proposals, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Proposals for Undergraduate Teaching Improvement Grants, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Publications, 1966-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Research Facilities Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt Middle School of the Arts, 1986-1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rules and Regulations of University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee and University of Wisconsin System, 1958-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Safety and Security, 1985-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Scholastic Appeals Committee
    - 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 1984-1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - School of Education, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - School of Fine Arts, Creation of, 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Schoolwide Scheduling Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Search and Screen Committee
    - Assistant Professor of Cello Search, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Assistant Professor of Film, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Assistant Professor of Theory and Composition Search, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Associate Dean Search, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Associate Professor Job Announcement, Forms A and B, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Dean of Fine Arts
      - 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 20-22)
    - Director of Bands Position Search, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Film Department Chairperson Search, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Film Junior Faculty Position, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Music Therapy Position Search, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Professor of String Pedagogy Search, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Technical Director Job Announcement, Form A and B, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Security Committee, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Signs for Fine Arts Facilities, 1985-1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - State Arts Festival, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Stowell House, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Student Services, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 32-33)
  - Student Strike, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Summer Arts Festival
    - 1961-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1-9)
    - 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 35-39)
  - Summer Evenings of Music, 1955-1971 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Sunday Evenings of Music, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Suppan, Adolph, Dean Emeritus, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Symphony on Campus Week, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Syllabi
    - Arts Alive Course 370-101, 1992-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Fine Arts at UWM Course 270-189, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Task Force for Long Range Planning
    - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Notes, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Technology Committee, 1992-1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Technology Research Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
  - Tenth Anniversary, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
  - Ten-Year Academic Program Intentions, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ten Years: Ten Artists, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Theatre of Color, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Thirtieth Anniversary, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Committee Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - University Arts Council
    - All Campus Arts Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Arts Resources Survey, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - University Arts Council Newsletter, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9-11)
  - University Ballet, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - University Ballet Concert, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - University Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - University Extension, 1967-1975 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  - University Honors Program, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - University of Wisconsin System Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - University of Wisconsin System Policies, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Urban Planning Master's Degree Proposal, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Urban Services, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Vanderbeek Workshop, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Very Special Arts Wisconsin, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Vilas Festival of Music, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Vilas String Quartet, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Welcome Week/Fall Orientation Activities, 1995-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin Art Education Association, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Wisconsin Artists Calendars, 1936-1938 (Box 8)
  - Wisconsin Painters and Sculptors Exhibition, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Wisconsin Press Photographers Association/Alfred Eisenstaedt Show, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Women in the Arts Celebration/Wisconsin Women in the Arts Organization, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Workshops, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Planning Documents, Program Review and Accreditation Files, and Subject Files, 1978-2016, Accession 2016-008; 16.4 cubic ft. (17 boxes) and 20 digital text files (0.336 MB); The accession includes budget and planning documents for Peck School of the Arts as a whole, individual program review files for the constituent departments of PSOA (Art, Performing Arts, Dance, Music, Film, and Theatre), as well as subject files on issues of particular interest to the dean, such as the 2012-2013 Year of the Arts celebration, the construction and renovation of the Kenilworth Square building, publicity for the Fine Arts Quartet and Summer Evenings of Music, and the School's relationship with the Slovenian Arts Council. Of interest in the budget files is the School's official response to the 2009-2010 state budget crisis.
  - Planning and Budget Documents
    - 1981-1995 (Box 1)
    - 1988-1993 (Box 2)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 3)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 4)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 5)
    - 2000-2004 (Box 6)
    - 2003-2008 (Box 7)
    - 2008-2014 (Box 8)
  - Program Reviews and Accreditation
    - Art, Graduate and Undergraduate, 1978-2013 (Box 9)
    - Dance, Graduate and Undergraduate, 1978-2012 (Box 10)
    - Performing Arts MFA, 1978-1998 (Box 10)
    - Film, Graduate and Undergraduate, 1974-2005 (Box 10)
    - Inter-Arts BFA, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Music, Graduate and Undergraduate, 1977 (Box 11)
    - National Academy of Schools of Music (NASM) Music Accreditation Review, 1988-2013 (Box 12)
    - Theatre, Undergraduate, 1998-2007 (Box 12)
  - Subject Files
    - Alumni Association
      - Asawa, Ruth, PSOA Distinguished Alumna, 1998 (Box 12)
      - PSOA Alumni Awards, 1996-2012 (Box 12)
      - PSOA Alumni Board and Events, 1995-1998 (Box 12)
      - UWM Alumni College, undated (Box 13)
      - UWM Alumni Event, "Backstage at Zelazo," 2002 (Box 13)
    - Dean's Advisory Council, 1986-1989 (Box 13)
    - Design Research Institute, 2011 (Box 13)
    - Facilities, 1988-2010 (Box 13)
    - Fine Arts Quartet
      - Announcements, Flyers, Photos, 1980-2016 (Box 13)
      - Clippings and Articles, 1980-2016 (Box 14)
      - Clippings and Programs, 1980-2016 (Box 14)
      - Press Releases, 1980-2016 (Box 14)
      - Programs, 1984-2008 (Box 14)
      - Season Brochures, 1984-2008 (Box 14)
      - Season Brochures for Summer Evenings of Music, 1980-2015 (Box 14)
    - Graduation Convocation Programs, 2006-2016 (Box 14)
    - Grand Viennese Ball, 1979-2008 (Box 14)
    - Homecoming, UWM, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
    - Kenilworth Open Studios, 2007-2012 (Box 14)
    - Kenilworth Square East Project Redevelopment Files, 2000-2007 (Box 15)
    - LGBT Film Festival Brochures, 1995-2015 (Box 15)
    - Neighborhood Block Party, UWM, 2000 (Box 15)
    - Open House, UWM, 1995-2012 (Box 15)
    - PSOA Pre-College Summer Arts Camp/Teen University, 2001-2002 (Box 16)
    - Showdown at Turner Hall, 2004 (Box 16)
    - Slovenian Arts Council, 1983-2008 (Box 16)
    - Spatial City Exhibit, 2009-2010 (Box 16)
    - Ventilation Assessment and Health and Safety Report, Art Building, 1992-1999 (Box 16)
    - Vilas Trust Grants, 1973-2013 (Box 17)
    - Year of the Arts, 2012-2013 (Box 17)